needsthesupermarket.com 2016-06-23

# Privacy Policy - Needsthesupermarket.com

**Privacy Policy**

At needsthesupermarket.com, we promise to secure your personal information you share with us in good faith. This privacy policy explains the types of information we gather, how it is protected, what we do with it and how you can correct or change information. By shopping at needsthesupermarket.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Note: Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically. Your use of needsthesupermarket.com means that you accept the practices described in this Privacy and Security Policy as changed from time to time.

#### Information collected:

As part of the registration process on the Site, needsthesupermarket.com may collect the following personally identifiable information about you: Name including First and Last name, Alternate Email Address, Mobile /Phone Number and Contact Details, Postal code, Demographic profile (like your age, gender, occupation, education, address etc.) and information about the pages on the site you visit/access, the links you click on the site, the number of times you access the page and any such browsing information.

#### Information Usage:

We will use your information to provide and personalize our service. We will also use your information to communicate with your and send you offer and news about needsthesupermarket.com products and services. We may contact you by post, email, telephone or fax for these purposes. Personal information is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes, other than the mandatory information that our online payment gateway providers require for risk monitoring purposes.

#### Change of information:

You may change your personal information at any point of time through My Account page.

#### Cookies:

Cookies are small pieces of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser. By accepting cookies, you can take full advantage of our site shopping experience. Needsthesupermarket.com also receives and stores certain types of information whenever you interact with us through the use of "cookies."

#### Security:

Security is our prime concern, thus all Credit card and Debit card payments on needsthesupermarket.com are processed through secure and trusted payment gateways managed by leading banks.

#### Other Websites & Links:

Needsthesupermarket.com may contain links to other web sites which are outside our control and, are not covered by our Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy. Needsthesupermarket.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites.

#### Policy Updates:

Needsthesupermarket.com reserves the right to change or update this policy at any time. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to the Site.
